Catholic Charities USA
The American Catholic Research Center and University Archives
- Series 4: Committee Files, 1920-2007; (71 Boxes)
  - Subseries 4.3: Conference of Religious, 1920-1973; (12 Boxes)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Commission on Families and Children (1), 1961, 1964-1967 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Commission on Families and Children (2), 1961, 1964-1967 (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Commission on Families and Children (3), 1961, 1964-1967 (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Commission on Families and Children (4), 1961, 1964-1967 (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Commission on Families and Children, 1964 (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Commission on Aging-Resources (1), 1963-1967 (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Commission on Aging-Resources (2), 1963-1967 (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Commission on Aging-Resources (3), 1963-1967 (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Commission on Aging-Resources (4), 1963-1967 (Box 160, Folder 9)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Annual Meeting (1), 1959-1965 (Box 160, Folder 10)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Annual Meeting (2), 1959-1965 (Box 160, Folder 11)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: South Eastern Regional Meeting, 1959-1964 (Box 160, Folder 12)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Questionnaire Replies - South Eastern Regional Meeting, 1964 (Box 160, Folder 13)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Adoption (CWL Standards), 1964 (Box 160, Folder 14)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Card Listing of Catholic Charities, 1965 (Box 160, Folder 15)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Fee Charging, 1959 (Box 160, Folder 16)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Group Care, 1965 (Box 160, Folder 17)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Group Living, 1964-1965 (Box 160, Folder 18)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Wage Home, 1965 (Box 160, Folder 19)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Directory of Catholic Maternity Homes, 1965-1966 (Box 160, Folder 20)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Family and Children, 1964-1966 (Box 160, Folder 21)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Catholic Maternity Homes Questionnaire (1), 1966 (Box 160, Folder 22)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Catholic Maternity Homes Questionnaire (2), 1966 (Box 160, Folder 23)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Catholic Maternity Homes Questionnaire (3), 1966 (Box 160, Folder 24)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Catholic Maternity Homes Questionnaire (4), 1966 (Box 160, Folder 25)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Catholic Maternity Homes Questionnaire (5), 1966 (Box 160, Folder 26)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Catholic Maternity Homes Questionnaire (6), 1966 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Catholic Maternity Homes Questionnaire (7), 1966 (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Report of Educational Programs in Catholic Maternity Homes, 1966 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Catholic Maternity Homes-Mailing List, 1963 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Guides for Services to Juvenile Delinquents, 1962-1963 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Membership Committee, 1968 (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Corcoran Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Quarterly Meetings, 1967-1968 (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: General Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 161, Folder 9)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Marian Visiting Training Material, 1961-1965 (Box 161, Folder 10)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Commission on Aging (1), 1965 (Box 161, Folder 11)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Commission on Aging (2), 1965 (Box 161, Folder 12)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Statistical Data - NIMH, 1963-1964 (Box 161, Folder 13)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: FSA Stat Reports, 1961-1966 (Box 161, Folder 14)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Family Service Statistics, 1961-1966 (Box 161, Folder 15)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: Traveller's Aid, 1961-1963 (Box 161, Folder 16)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: National Study Group on Statistical Reporting (1), 1963-1969 (Box 161, Folder 17)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: National Study Group on Statistical Reporting (2), 1963-1969 (Box 161, Folder 18)
    - Conference of Religious New York Office: National Study Group on Statistical Reporting (3), 1963-1969 (Box 161, Folder 19)
  - Subseries 4.4: Committee on Professional Education for Social Work, 1934-1949; (1 Box)
    - Schedules - Diocese, 1934 (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - Report of Study of Professional Education for Social Work (1), 1936 (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - Report of Study of Professional Education for Social Work (2), 1936 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (1), 1935 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (2), 1935 (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (3), 1935 (Box 162, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (4), 1935 (Box 162, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - Fr. Lauerman to Msgr. Wagner, 1935 (Box 162, Folder 9)
    - Good Shepherd League, 1931-1932 (Box 162, Folder 10)
    - Schedules - Diocese (1), 1935 (Box 162, Folder 11)
    - Schedules - Diocese (2), 1935 (Box 162, Folder 12)
    - Schedules - Diocese (3), 1935 (Box 162, Folder 13)
    - Schedules - Diocese (4), 1935 (Box 162, Folder 14)
    - Schedules - Archdiocese, 1934 (Box 162, Folder 15)
    - Committee on Education for Social Work (1), 1946-1947 (Box 162, Folder 16)
    - Committee on Education for Social Work (2), 1946-1947 (Box 162, Folder 17)
    - Summaries of Dissertations, 1948 (Box 162, Folder 18)
    - Committee on Education for Social Work, 1950 (Box 162, Folder 19)
    - Abstracts of Theses, 1948 (Box 162, Folder 20)
    - Committee on Education for Social Work - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 162, Folder 21)
    - O'Conner, Williams, 1949 (Box 162, Folder 22)
    - Teaching Applications, 1949 (Box 162, Folder 23)
    - Distribution of Case Records, 1949 (Box 162, Folder 24)
    - Minutes of Meetings (1), 1948-1949 (Box 162, Folder 25)
    - Minutes of Meetings (2), 1948-1949 (Box 162, Folder 26)
    - Letters to Social Service Departments of Catholic Hospitals, 1949 (Box 162, Folder 27)
    - Kurt Case, 1948 (Box 162, Folder 28)
    - W Case, 1947-1948 (Box 162, Folder 29)
    - Evaluation Sheets, 1948 (Box 162, Folder 30)
    - American Association of Schools of Social Work - Family Service Association - Committee Teaching Records, 1946-1951 (Box 162, Folder 31)
    - Case Records, 1948-1949 (Box 162)
      Multiple folders, 32-56. RESTRICTED.
  - Subseries 4.5: Committee on Aging, 1970-2001; (8 Boxes)
    - Aged Material - Miscellaneous, 1946-1947 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Care of the Elderly, 1949 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Committee on the Aged - Articles (1), 1947 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Committee on the Aged - Articles (2), 1947 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - Committee on the Aged - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - Committee on the Aged - Minutes of Meetings, 1947-1948 (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - Institutional Facilities for the Care of the Aged - John J. Griffin, 1947 (Box 163, Folder 7)
    - Committee on the Aged - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 163, Folder 8)
    - Committee on the Aged - Miscellaneous, 1948 (Box 163, Folder 9)
    - Conference on Community Programs for the Aging, 1949 (Box 163, Folder 10)
    - Conference on Community Programs for Sheltered Care of the Aged, 1946 (Box 163, Folder 11)
    - Conference on Community Programs for Sheltered Care of the Aged, 1948 (Box 163, Folder 12)
    - Federal Council of Churches in America, 1948 (Box 163, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence - John J. Griffin, 1946-1948 (Box 163, Folder 14)
    - Material on Pamphlet on Aged, 1949 (Box 163, Folder 15)
    - O'Grady, John - Current Problems in Catholic Institutional Care of the Aged, 1948 (Box 163, Folder 16)
    - Old Age and Survivors' Insurance Social Security Act, 1943-1945 (Box 163, Folder 17)
    - Protestant Collaboration on Problems of the Aged, 1946-1947 (Box 163, Folder 18)
    - Relationship of Catholic School to Catholic Social Agency re: Problem Children - Joint Study, 1945-1946 (Box 163, Folder 19)
    - "Relative's Responsibility", 1949 (Box 163, Folder 20)
    - Reports on Aged Institutions Visited during 1944, 1945, and 1946 (Box 163, Folder 21)
    - Study of Institutions of the Aged, 1946 (Box 163, Folder 22)
    - Religious Ministry to Older People, n.d. (Box 163, Folder 23)
    - Study of the Aged - Marion Mulligan, 1948 (Box 163, Folder 24)
    - Study of the Aged - Fr. Brown, 1949 (Box 163, Folder 25)
    - The Aged - Miscellaneous Correspondence (1), 1956-1961 (Box 163, Folder 26)
    - The Aged - Miscellaneous Correspondence (2), 1956-1961 (Box 163, Folder 27)
    - 'The Aging of Three Parishes', 1958 (Box 163, Folder 28)
    - Bibliography on Aging, 1961 (Box 163, Folder 29)
    - Boston Study on Spiritual Care of Children Away from their own Homes, 1952-1953 (Box 163, Folder 30)
    - Clergy Under OASI, 1953-1961 (Box 163, Folder 31)
    - Federal Income Tax Procedures for Child Placing Agencies-Foster Parents, 1944-1952 (Box 163, Folder 32)
    - Old Age and Survivors' Insurance - Social Security Act, 1951-1952 (Box 163, Folder 33)
    - Older Citizens' Survey - Washington, D.C., 1960 (Box 163, Folder 34)
    - One Drive Community Financing, 1950 (Box 163, Folder 35)
    - Parish Study of the Aging - Buffalo, New York, 1956 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - Private versus Federated Fund Raising, 1951-1954 (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Relative Hospitality in ACD and OAA (1), 1951 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Relative Hospitality in ACD and OAA (2), 1951 (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Questionnaire Study of Scholarships and other Forms of Assistance Made Available for Social Work, 1956 (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - Study of Retirement Plans and Fringe Benefits of Workers in Catholic Agencies, 1955-1956 (Box 164, Folder 6)
    - Study of Health Needs of the Aging, Committee on - Msgr. Fischer, Chairman, 1960 (Box 164, Folder 7)
    - Study of the Aging - St. Louis - General (1), 1953 (Box 164, Folder 8)
    - Study of the Aging - St. Louis - General (2), 1953 (Box 164, Folder 9)
    - Study of the Aging - St. Louis - General, 1955 (Box 164, Folder 10)
    - Study of the Aging - St. Louis - General (1), 1953-1955 (Box 164, Folder 11)
    - Study of the Aging - St. Louis - General (2), 1953-1955 (Box 164, Folder 12)
    - Study of the Aging - St. Louis - Background Problems, Correspondence, Meetings, ca. 1953-1955 (Box 164, Folder 13)
    - Study of the Aging - St. Louis - Final Report, ca. 1955 (Box 164, Folder 14)
    - Study of the Aging - St. Louis - Parish Study (Legion), ca. 1953-1955 (Box 164, Folder 15)
    - Study of the Aging - St. Louis - Survey, etc., ca. 1953-1955 (Box 164, Folder 16)
    - Social Security - General (1), 1949-1954 (Box 164, Folder 17)
    - Social Security - General (2), 1949-1954 (Box 164, Folder 18)
    - Social Security - General (3), 1949-1954 (Box 164, Folder 19)
    - Social Security - General (4), 1949-1954 (Box 164, Folder 20)
    - Social Security - 'An Analysis of the Present Federal Social Security Program for the Aged and the Proposal of the Chamber of Commerce of the United States,' by Rev. John O'Grady, ca. 1954 (Box 164, Folder 21)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Admission, Intake, 1955 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Administration of Home for the Aging, 1947-1949 (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Bibliography, 1950-1955 (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Community Surveys and Planning, 1951-1954 (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Conference on Aging, Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1954 (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Conference on Aging, Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1955 (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Catholic Homes and Agencies, 1954 (Box 165, Folder 7)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Counseling and Casework Services, 1951-1954 (Box 165, Folder 8)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Economics of Employment, Retirement, OAA, OASI, 1954-1955 (Box 165, Folder 9)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Family, 1954 (Box 165, Folder 10)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Foster Care, 1952 (Box 165, Folder 11)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - General Material Dealing with Standards (1), 1954-1955 (Box 165, Folder 12)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - General Material Dealing with Standards (2), 1954-1955 (Box 165, Folder 13)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - General Material Dealing with Standards (3), 1954-1955 (Box 165, Folder 14)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Health (1), 1949-1954 (Box 165, Folder 15)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Health (2), 1949-1954 (Box 165, Folder 16)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Homemaker's Service, 1950-1953 (Box 165, Folder 17)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Institute, Conferences, 1952-1955 (Box 165, Folder 18)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Jewish Agencies (1), 1952-1955 (Box 165, Folder 19)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Jewish Agencies (2), 1952-1955 (Box 165, Folder 20)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Recreation and Cultural Activities (1), 1952-1955 (Box 165, Folder 21)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Recreation and Cultural Activities (2), 1952-1955 (Box 165, Folder 22)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Religion, 1946-1954 (Box 165, Folder 23)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Research, 1954 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Sample Forms, 1949 (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Visits and Interviews, 1954 (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Volunteers, 1955-1956 (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Replies from Directors on Architectural Plans, Fire Regulations, etc. (1), 1954 (Box 166, Folder 5)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Replies from Directors on Architectural Plans, Fire Regulations, etc. (2), 1954 (Box 166, Folder 6)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Living Arrangements and Housing (1), 1952-1955 (Box 166, Folder 7)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Living Arrangements and Housing (2), 1952-1955 (Box 166, Folder 8)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Letters from Catholic Editors re: Story on Aging by Lennon, 1954 (Box 166, Folder 9)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Letters from Catholic Bishops re: Report on Study on Aging by Lennon, 1954 (Box 166, Folder 10)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Meetings on Aging, 1955 (Box 166, Folder 11)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Miscellaneous Correspondence on Study on the Aging, 1954-1955 (Box 166, Folder 12)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Miscellaneous, 1954-1955 (Box 166, Folder 13)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Non Resident Aid, 1952-1953 (Box 166, Folder 14)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Protestant Homes for the Aged, 1952-1955 (Box 166, Folder 15)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Psychology and Psychiatry, 1954 (Box 166, Folder 16)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Rates, 1955 (Box 166, Folder 17)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Study of the Aging, 1954-1955 (Box 166, Folder 18)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Proposed Parish Study of the Aging, Denver, 1954 (Box 166, Folder 19)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Parish Study of the Aging, Detroit, 1954 (Box 166, Folder 20)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Parish Study of the Aging, Chicago, 1954 (Box 166, Folder 21)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Institute on Meeting the Problems of the Aging, St. Louis University, 1956 (Box 166, Folder 22)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Study on the Aging, Cleveland - Memos and Letters, 1954-1955 (Box 166, Folder 23)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - The Aging - Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 166, Folder 24)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Programming for the Aging - Miscellaneios Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 166, Folder 25)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Programming for the Aging, 1951-1952 (Box 166, Folder 26)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Programming for the Aging, 1949-1950 (Box 166, Folder 27)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Msgr. O'Grady's Notes on the Aging, 1948-1949 (Box 166, Folder 28)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - The Study of Later Maturity, University of Chicago, 1951 (Box 166, Folder 29)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Retirement Research Studies and Pre-Retirement Planning Project, 1953 (Box 166, Folder 30)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Jennings Hall Survey (1), 1954 (Box 166, Folder 31)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Jennings Hall Survey (2), 1954 (Box 166, Folder 32)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Jennings Hall Survey (3), 1954 (Box 166, Folder 33)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Jennings Hall Survey (4), 1954 (Box 166, Folder 34)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Jennings Hall, ca. 1955 (Box 166, Folder 35)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Jennings Hall - Questionnaire, ca. 1955 (Box 166, Folder 36)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Jennings Hall - Study of Aging, ca. 1955 (Box 166, Folder 37)
    - Fr. John J. Lennon - Jennings Hall - Report of Study of Aging, 1954-1955 (Box 166, Folder 38)
    - Committee on Aging - Legislative Material, 1968 (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Aging - Catholic Hospital Association Liaison Committee Material, 1967-1968 (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - Committee on Aging - Survey on Administrators of Nursing Homes, 1968 (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - Committee on Aging - Model Law - Licensing, 1968 (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - Committee on Aging - Licensing Testimony, 1968-1969 (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - Committee on Aging - Licensing of Nursing Home Administrators, 1968-1969 (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - Committee on Aging - Aging News Notes, 1964-1969 (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - Committee on Aging - Minutes, 1967 (Box 167, Folder 8)
    - Committee on Aging - Survey on Homes for the Aged, 1967 (Box 167, Folder 9)
    - Committee on Aging - Institutions, 1967 (Box 167, Folder 10)
    - Committee on Aging - Meeting Minutes, 1968 (Box 167, Folder 11)
    - Committee on Aging - Survey for Priest Institute, 1968 (Box 167, Folder 12)
    - Committee on Aging - Meeting Minutes, 1969 (Box 167, Folder 13)
    - Committee on Aging - Guides Material, 1969 (Box 167, Folder 14)
    - Committee on Aging - Tax Reform Material, 1969 (Box 167, Folder 15)
    - Committee on Aging - Members of Commission, 1970 (Box 167, Folder 16)
    - Committee on Aging - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 167, Folder 17)
    - Commission on Aging - General, 1974 (Box 167, Folder 18)
    - Commission on Aging - General, 1975-1976 (Box 167, Folder 19)
    - Commission on Aging - Operating Guidelines, 1977 (Box 167, Folder 20)
    - Commission on Aging - General, 1977 (Box 167, Folder 21)
    - Commission on Aging - General, 1978 (Box 167, Folder 22)
    - Commission on Aging - Programs and Workshops, 1978 (Box 167, Folder 23)
    - Commission on Aging - Nominating Committee, 1978, 1980 (Box 167, Folder 24)
    - Commission on Aging - General, 1979 (Box 167, Folder 25)
    - Commission on Aging - General, 1980 (Box 167, Folder 26)
    - Commission on Aging - General, 1981 (Box 167, Folder 27)
    - Commission on Aging - Social Security, 1981 (Box 167, Folder 28)
    - Commission on Aging - Nominations Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 167, Folder 29)
    - Commission on Aging - Printed Material, 1981 (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - Commission on Aging - White House Conference on Children and Youth, 1981 (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Commission on Aging - Senator Paul Laxalt and Protection of Family Act, 1980 (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Commission on Aging - National Advisory Committee, 1980 (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - Commission on Aging - Pro-Family Information, 1978-1980 (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - Commission on Aging - Plan for White House Conference, 1980 (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - Commission on Aging - Press for White House Conference, 1980 (Box 168, Folder 7)
    - Commission on Aging - White House Conference on the Handicapped, 1976 (Box 168, Folder 8)
    - Commission on Aging - Coalition for Correcting Abuses in Nursing Homes, 1980 (Box 168, Folder 9)
    - Commission on Aging - National Council on Aging Mission Statement, 1981 (Box 168, Folder 10)
    - Commission on Aging - Help the Aged Organization, 1982 (Box 168, Folder 11)
    - Commission on Aging - National Council on Aging, 1971-1980 (Box 168, Folder 12)
    - White House Conference on Families - Final Results, Los Angelos, 1980 (Box 168, Folder 13)
    - White House Conference on Families - Minneapolis Meeting, 1980 (Box 168, Folder 14)
    - White House Conference on Families - Baltimore, 1980 (Box 168, Folder 15)
    - White House Conference on Families - Background Information, 1980 (Box 168, Folder 16)
    - White House Conference on Families - Coalition (1), 1980 (Box 168, Folder 17)
    - White House Conference on Families - Coalition (2), 1980 (Box 168, Folder 18)
    - White House Conference on Families - General Information, 1980 (Box 168, Folder 19)
    - Commission on Aging - NVOILA, 1980-1981 (Box 168, Folder 20)
    - Commission on Aging - NVOILA Grant Proposal, 1980 (Box 168, Folder 21)
    - Commission on Aging - NVOILA Task Committee, 1980 (Box 168, Folder 22)
    - Commission on Aging - National Voluntary Organizations Steering Committee-Services, 1971-1979 (Box 168, Folder 23)
    - Commission on Aging - Albany, New York, Aging Services, 1980 (Box 168, Folder 24)
    - Commission on Aging - Catholic University Aging Center, 1974-1979 (Box 168, Folder 25)
    - Commission on Aging - Day Care for the Elderly, 1974-1975 (Box 168, Folder 26)
    - Commission on Aging - GTE Companion Service, 1978 (Box 168, Folder 27)
    - Commission on Aging - Project VIE Junior League, 1978 (Box 168, Folder 28)
    - Commission on Aging - Sisters Retirement Program, 1979 (Box 168, Folder 29)
    - Commission on Aging - United States Catholic Conference and Aging, 1979-1980 (Box 168, Folder 30)
    - Commission on Aging - Elderly Low Vision Services, 1981 (Box 168, Folder 31)
    - Commission on Aging - Hospice Information, 1979 (Box 168, Folder 32)
    - Commission on Aging - Housing Information, 1977 (Box 168, Folder 33)
    - Commission on Aging - Current Aging, 1981 (Box 168, Folder 34)
    - National Interfaith Coalition on Aging (NICA) - Resource Library, 1980 (Box 168, Folder 35)
    - National Interfaith Coalition on Aging (NICA) - White House Conference on Aging Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 168, Folder 36)
    - National Interfaith Coalition on Aging (NICA), 1982 (Box 168, Folder 37)
    - National Interfaith Coalition on Aging (NICA - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 168, Folder 38)
    - National Interfaith Coalition on Aging (NICA - Board Business, 1980 (Box 168, Folder 39)
    - National Interfaith Coalition on Aging (NICA) - Spiritual Well Being, 1981 (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - National Interfaith Coalition on Aging (NICA) - General, 1971-1978 (Box 169, Folder 2)
    - National Interfaith Coalition on Aging (NICA) - Final Report, 1976 (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - National Interfaith Coalition on Aging (NICA) - General, ca. 1975-1977 (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - National Interfaith Coalition on Aging (NICA) - General, 1979 (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - National Interfaith Coalition on Aging (NICA) - GIST Program, 1980 (Box 169, Folder 6)
    - National Interfaith Coalition on Aging (NICA) - Dying and Death, ca. 1982 (Box 169, Folder 7)
    - Commission on Aging - White House Conference on Families News Kit, 1980 (Box 169, Folder 8)
    - Commission on Aging - Follow Up Ideas - Project's Information White House Conference on Families, 1980 (Box 169, Folder 9)